/*
   Friday, July 21, 201711:32:38 PM
   User: 
   Server: DESKTOP-BHBB5O1\SQLEXPRESS
   Database: MyStore
   Application: 
*/

'Customers' table saved successfully
'Orders' table
- Unable to create relationship 'FK_Orders_Customers'.  
Cannot create the foreign key "FK_Orders_Customers" with the SET NULL referential action, because one or more referencing columns are not nullable.
Could not create constraint or index. See previous errors.

